Yes, I have to take some extra footage now.
はい、今からね、ちょっとおまけ映像撮らなきゃいけないんです
However, if you are a phone lover, I have brought you this one.
けど、 電話好きのあなたに、わざわざこれをちょっと持ってき
I did.
ました
picture!?
え!?
This is it, the phone.
これね、電話
Do you understand?
分かる?
Amazing!
すご!
Warts and warts, warts and warts.
いぼいぼですよ、いぼいぼ
It's all warts.
いぼいぼだよ
Have you seen it?
見たことある?
No, not for the first time.
ない、初めて
do not have?
ない?
good.
よかった
Come on.
さあ、ね
Try moving it a little.
ちょっと動かしてみて
This feels good.
気持ちよさそう、これ
Right?
でしょ?
So, I thought I'd watch it make you feel better.
それでちょっとね、気持ちよくなってもらうところ見ようかなと思
Yes, but first,
うん ですけど、 ちょっとまず、
I'll get you some panties.
おパンティをもらいます
Panties?
おパンティ?
I'll get you some panties.
おパンティをもらいます
Why would it be better to have a direct line?
なんで、直通だったほうがいいじゃん
Hey, what are you going to do with that?
ちょっとね、それを何にして
Just show me, show me.
ちょっと見せて、見せて
I tightened it quite weakly?
結構弱めから締めた?
Yeah.
うん
is that so?
そうですか?
This is really good.
これ、めっちゃいい
Is it really good?
めっちゃいい?
Yeah.
うん
How much is the power balance now?
今、パワーアバランスにとどれくらい?
3 stages.
3段階
picture?
え?
what?
何?
Parallel of that phone.
その電話のパラレル
Ah, strength?
あ、強さ?
This is still the lowest.
まだこれ、一番低い
After a while, I will increase my power,
少ししたら、自分からパワーを上げるよって、
Shall we raise it?
上げていきましょうか
I'm coming.
いきますよ
Increase power?
パワーを上げる?
Shall I raise it?
上げちゃう?
oh.
おー
Ugh.
うー
What do you think?
どうだよ
Start a little lower,
ちょっと、低いところから始めて、
So I powered up and went.
で、パワーアップして、行っちゃった
Have you gone?
行っちゃった?
Isn't it Max?
マックスじゃないですか?
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Did you go?
行きました?
yes.
はい
Thank you for your hard work.
お疲れさまでございました